<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Warsaw TourGuideApp</string>
    <string name="poi">Points of Interest</string>
    <string name="historic">Historic Sites</string>
    <string name="nature">Nature&amp;Parks</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>

    <!-- Points of Interest -->
    <string name="old_town">Old Town</string>
    <string name="old_town_desc">
        Surrounded by beautiful seventeenth- and eighteenth-century merchants\'
        houses, this lively square is filled with street vendors, cafes, shops,
        galleries and some of Warsaw\'s top restaurants.
    </string>
    <string name="castle">Castle Square</string>
    <string name="castle_desc">
        Located in Old Town, this picturesque open plaza was built in 1821 and features
        the King Zygmunt III column in its center.
    </string>
    <string name="palace_wilanow">Wilanów Palace</string>
    <string name="palace_wilanow_desc">
        Wilanów Palace survived Poland\'s partitions and both World Wars, and so serves as
        a reminder of the culture of the Polish state as it was before the misfortunes
        of the 18th century.
    </string>

    <string name="palace_culture">Palace of Culture and Science</string>
    <string name="palace_culture_desc">
        Considered Poland\'s highest building, this monumental skyscraper (circa 1955)
        contains 42 floors at a height of 230.68 meters (756.82 feet),
        topped with a needle height of 43 meters (141.08 feet).
    </string>
    <!-- End Points of Interests-->

    <!-- Historical Places -->
    <string name="uprising_museum">Warsaw Uprising Museum</string>
    <string name="uprising_museum_desc">
        The Warsaw Rising Museum was opened on the 60th anniversary of the outbreak
        of fighting in Warsaw. The Museum is a tribute of Warsaw’s residents to those
        who fought and died for independent Poland and its free capital.
    </string>
    <string name="palace_lazienki">Lazienki Palace</string>
    <string name="palace_lazienki_desc">
        Built by King Stanislaw August Poniatowski during the second half of the 18th century,
        this neoclassical palace once served as a royal residence that is surrounded with ponds,
        canals and magnificent park-like grounds.
    </string>
    <string name="royal_castle">The Royal Castle</string>
    <string name="royal_castle_desc">
        Serving as the central building of the Polish Commonwealth for many centuries,
        this castle was rebuilt after it was dynamited by German troops after the Warsaw uprising,
        and has been rebuilt to recreate the original castle\'s 17th-century architecture and interiors.
    </string>
    <string name="krakowskie">Krakowskie Przedmiescie</string>
    <string name="krakowskie_desc">
        This 2.5 mile "Road of Kings" leads from The Royal Castle (Old Town) to Wilanow Palace.
    </string>
    <!-- End Historical Places-->

    <!-- Nature & Parks -->
    <string name="lazienki">Lazienki - Royal Residence Park</string>
    <string name="lazienki_desc">
        Magnificent palatial and garden complex was built by King Stanislaw August Poniatowski
        during the second half of the eighteenth century and features the neoclassical
        Palace on the Water (Lazienki Palace) surrounded by magnificent gardens, canals and ponds.
    </string>
    <string name="saxon_gardens">Saxon Gardens</string>
    <string name="saxon_gardens_desc">
        Once serving as the gardens of Saxon Palace, this magnificent park features
        shady tree-lined avenues, Baroque sculptures, an elegant 19-century fountain and
        the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, a grave reminder of Poland\'s recent past.
    </string>
    <string name="park_ujazdowski">Park Ujazdowski</string>
    <string name="park_ujazdowski_desc">
        Ujazdów Park (Polish: Park Ujazdowski) is one of the most picturesque parks of Warsaw, Poland.
        It borders Aleje Ujazdowskie (Ujazdów Avenue), with its many embassies and Sejm building.
    </string>
    <string name="park_skaryszewski">Park Skaryszewski</string>
    <string name="park_skaryszewski_desc">
        Skaryszewski Park is an urban, monumental park located in the Praga Południe district of Warsaw.
        The park was designed and created by Franciszek Szanior in 1905.
    </string>
    <!-- End Nature & Parks-->

    <!-- Restaurants -->
    <string name="stary_dom">Stary Dom</string>
    <string name="stary_dom_desc">
        The Stary Dom Restaurant refers back to the best traditions of Polish cuisine and welcoming
        atmosphere. The design alludes to traditional interiors connected with the home hearth.
        This makes the restaurant an ideal location for meetings of family and close friends.
        For non Poles it gives a taste of traditional Polish hospitality.
    </string>
    <string name="n31">N&#xb0;31</string>
    <string name="n31_desc">
        N31 restaurant&amp;bar is an authorial restaurant run by master chef Robert Sowa.
        The basic menu consists of traditional Polish meals with an international touch,
        served in an unusual way.
    </string>
    <string name="amber">Amber Room</string>
    <string name="amber_desc">
        Located within the charming Sobanski Palace on Avenue Ujazdowskie, perhaps the
        most prestigious street in Warsaw, the venue is an island of serenity,
        distinguishing itself as place that offers an atmosphere of soft elegance surrounded
        by the soothing environs of leafy trees and green parks. In Palac Sobanski,
        beside The Amber Room restaurant; the Polish Business Roundtable Club is located.
    </string>
    <string name="delicja">Delicja Polska</string>
    <string name="delicja_desc">
        Delicja Polska is a restaurant in Warsawoffering a unique atmosphere,
        created by its delicious traditional Polish cuisine, cozy and romantic interior
        and truly high restaurant service standard. We endeavor to serve tasty dishesthat satisfy
        and exceedour customers’ expectations.
    </string>
    <!-- Restaurants-->


</resources>
